[
  {
    "question":"¿Cuánto  es la suma de 8+5 ?",
    "answer":"13"
  },
  {
    "question":"¿Cuánto es la suma de 12-7 ?",
    "answer":"5"
  },
  {
    "question":"¿Cuánto es la suma de 4x6 ?",
    "answer":"24"
  },
  {
    "question":"¿Cuánto es la suma de 20\/4 ?",
    "answer":"5"
  },
  {
    "question":"¿Cuánto es la suma de 9+6 ?",
    "answer":"15"
  },
  {
    "question":"¿Cuánto es la suma de 15-8 ?",
    "answer":"7"
  },
  {
    "question":"¿Cuánto es la suma de 7x3 ?",
    "answer":"21"
  },
  {
    "question":"¿Cuánto es la suma de 9-3 ?",
    "answer":"6"
  },
  {
    "question":"¿Cuánto es la suma de 14+2 ?",
    "answer":"16"
  },
  {
    "question":"¿Cuánto es la suma de 10-4 ?",
    "answer":"6"
  }
]